Hanslowe, Kurt, Papers /4064
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kurt Hanslowe Papers
1945-1982
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Hanslowe, Kurt
/4064
13 cubic feet
13 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
3079882
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 16, 2015
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 22, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4297: ILR School Biography Files 6004: NAA Additional Records
Hanslowe, Kurt L.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Faculty.
3079882
- Federal Admin. Procedures Act (Box 1)
  - The Sovereign Employer and Its Employees (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Survey of State Legislation Affecting Public Employees and Notes (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Professor Hanslowe Notes and "Threatened Violence" Announcement (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - S.2810: A Bill Amending the NLRA with Respect to Emergency Labor Disputes, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Mr. Charles B. Rangel Proposed Act to Amend NYS Labor Law and Critiques, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ordinary Contingent Expenses and Budget Authorization: A Statement of Clarification by Charles A. Brind (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - NYS Acts: Intro S.1605, 4784, 874, Intro A.2970, 2772, 4078, Connecticut's Municipal Employee Relations Act, "Labor Relations Law" by Kurt Hanslowe, 1965- 1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - News Clippings and Brookings Institute Program, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Notes and Plans for ILR 0580 Course, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Reports and Papers: NYS Board of Education/School Boards, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "The US Experience in Collective Bargaining in Public Employment"- Arvid Anderson, Congressional Record (90th Congress) and News Clipping: NLRB, 1966- 1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Cornell University Announcements: General Information ('67), College of Arts and Sciences ('66-'67), Center for International Studies ('66-'67), Summer Session ('67), NYSSILR ('67-'69), 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Cornell Desk Book ('70), Orientation and Freshman Handbook ('66), Law at Cornell, 1966-1970 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Directory of Law Teachers, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Memoranda: On Campaign Literature, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Problem No. 3: Case before the FTC and General Legislation of the University Faculty, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - News Articles from NYT on Prostitution, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Annual Faculty Report Letter, ILR 602 Class List, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Sources of Financial Support for ILR Research and Notes, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Collegiate News and Views ('71), 1969 Seizure of Barton Incident, Misc. Papers and Personal Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Wolkinson, Ben: Thesis Chapters I- III, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Wolkinson, Ben: Thesis Chapters IV- VII, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Grad School of Business and Public Administration, Report: "Transmittal Letter and Introduction", 1968 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Adjudicatory System for Student Conduct ('68) and Summary of Division of Extension and Public Service ('71), 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - ILR Faculty Editorial Guidelines, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Notes on Wolkinson, Ben Thesis Defense, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Minutes of Meetings for University Faculty and in the Department of Collective Bargaining, Labor Law and Labor Movements, 1968-1972 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Salzburg Seminar Notes, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - ILR Letters and Memoranda, 1968-1972 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Speech by Robert McKersie and Faculty/Faculty- Council Meetings, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - ILR 580 Agency Reports, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Report and Paper to the Dean and Faculty and Analysis of Sovereignty and Public Sector Strike, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - The Public Review Board, International Union, UAW, Cases: 245, 247, 249, 250, 253, 257, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Misc. Papers, Records, and Announcements, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Letters, Memoranda, and Misc. Papers/Reports (Contains German), 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Scope and Contents
    German Language
  - NYSSILR Staff and Student Directory, Course Scheduling and Course Request Form, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Misc. Notes and ILR 602 Class List, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Thomson, A. W. J. Thesis Proposal and Outline (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Bibliography: Labor Management Relations Act, 1947 as Amended by the Labor- Management Reporting and Disclosure Act, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Wilhelm Weinberg Seminar, IL 581 Reading Assignment, Voluntary Labor Arbitration Rules, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Problems No. 1-9 of Class Written Assignment (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Misc. News Clippings on Cornell Student Conflict and Assorted Papers, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - NLRB Case Decisions and Orders, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Public Law 90-54, 90th Congress, S. J. Res. 81, "Joint Resolution", 1967 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Mr. Morse's Report and Individual Views Regarding the Railroad Shop Craft Dispute, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - UAW vs. NLRB (General Motors Corporation) US Court of Appeals, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Letters and Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Misc. Papers and Notes, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - New Rochelle, New York, Board of Education Materials, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Manual of Administrative Practices and Procedures ('61), "Your Career" Pamphlet, "Vital Speeches of the Day" ('65), 1961-1965 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Memo, Professor's Vite, and "Written Exercise No. 2" ILR 502, 1966-1971 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Summary of ILR Grad Students Data, Court Decisions Regarding Labor- Management Relations, Concert Series Papers, and Report of President's Review Committee on Employee- Management Relations in the Federal Service, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Washington State Board Against Discrimination: Howard Lewis and Jettie Murray vs. Ironworkers Local No.86: Cases: E-1074, E-1028, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Federal Admin. Procedures Act (Box 2)
  - Draft Statute: Article 19- I (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Federal Administrative Procedure Act, Chapter 19, 1001-1011 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Uniform Law Commissioners' Revised Model State Administration Procedure Act (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Public Hearing Attendees- Buffalo, Syracuse, Binghamton, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - New York State Senate Resolution No. 103, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Draft Administrative Procedure Act and Comments (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Massachusetts and West Virginia Administrative Procedure Acts, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - State of New York Workmen's Compensation Board Correspondence, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - State of New York Law Revision Commission Reports, Recommendations and Study, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Revised Model Administrative Procedures Act, Legislative Research Commission, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Draft Report on Administrative Procedure Act (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - New York State Senate Resolution No. 9, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Legislative Resolution/Order and First and Second Drafts of Report on Administrative Procedure Act by Law Revision Commission, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Draft Report on Administrative Procedure Act and Legislative Document: Report of the Law Revision Commission for 1965 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Comments, Reports, and Drafts, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Constitutional Law with Respect to Administrative Adjudication- Ralph D. Semerad (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Constitutional Law with Respect to Administrative Adjudication- Ralph D. Semerad and Administrative Procedure Legislation Among the States (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Report of Administrative Law Committee of New York State Bar Association and "List of Reports of the Administrative Conference of the United States", 1963- 1964 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Selected Reports of the Administrative Conference of the United States, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Correspondence and publications (Box 3)
  - New Means of Land Mobile Communications: Some Legal Implications- Hanslowe (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Union Security in Public Employment: of Free Riding and Free Association- Hanslowe, Dunn, and Erstling (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence- '67-'68, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence- '68-'69, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence- '68-'69, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Hanslowe Correspondence- '71, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Hanslowe- Correspondence- '72, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Hanslowe- Correspondence- '73, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Hanslowe- Correspondence- '74, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Hanslowe-Correspondence- '75, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Union Security in Public Employment: of Free Riding and Free Association- Hanslowe, Dunn, and Erstling Ch. I-VI and Footnotes (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Hanslowe- Correspondence- '74, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Hanslowe-Correspondence- '76, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Hanslowe- Correspondence- '78, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Hanslowe- Correspondence- '79, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Ch. 3: "Cambridge and St. Louis in the 1870's" from Brandeis: A Free Man's Life (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - "Journal of Legal Education: The Second and Third Years of Law Study"- Walter Gellhorn, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Harvard Law Record- Nov. 12th Vol. 39 No. 6, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Hanslowe- Correspondence- '78, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Hanslowe- Correspondence- Related to New Faculty Search, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Liberty in Danger- Macneil and Hanslowe (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Minn. Vs. John F. Biron: Police Interrogation, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Labor Relations Law, 1960- Hanslowe and Joint Legislative Committee on Industrial and Labor Conditions Repot, 1962-1963, 1960-1963 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Report of Survey of Various Aspects of New York State Labor Relations Policy Undertaken for Commissioner Catherwood- Hanslowe, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - The Division of Labor and Management Practices, Dept. of Labor Report and "Corrupt and Anti-Democratic Practices in Unions" (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals, Second Circuit: Black- Clawson Company vs. International Association of Machinists, Lodge 355, District 137- Opinion, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - USA before the NLRB in the Matter of: Cornell University and the Association of Cornell Employees- Libraries, Case No. 3-RC-4768, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Western Addition Community vs. NLRB Case Overview and Remarks, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Teamsters Local 413, Truck Drivers Union vs. NLRB Case Overview, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - NLRB vs. J. Weingarten, Inc. Case Overview, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO vs. NLRB Case Overview, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - News and Background Information: Labor Relations Reporter, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Summary and Outlines of Remarks by Jay Siegel and Robert Lewis, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Employee Retirement Income Security Act of 1974, Outline of Provisions- Robert E. Nagle (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Correspondence, 1950-1971 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence I- '50-'56, 1950-1956 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence II- '50-'56, 1950-1956 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence III- '50-'56, 1950-1956 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence- '58, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence- '59, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence- 1960 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence- 1961 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence- '62, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence- 1962 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence- Jan. '63- June '63, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence- Jan. '63- June '63, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence- July '63- Dec. '63, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence- July '63- Dec. '63, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence- Jan. '64- June '64, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence- Jan '64- June '64, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence- July 1964- Dec. 1964 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence- 1965 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence- Jan. 1966- June 1966 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence- July 1966- Dec. 1966 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence- Jan. 1967- June 1967 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence- July 1967- Dec. 1967 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence- Jan. 1968- June 1968 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence- July 1968- Dec. 1968 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence- Jan. 1969- June 1969 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence- July 1969- Dec. 1969 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence- Jan. 1970- June 1970 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence- June 1970- June 1971, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence- June 1971 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence- Hanslowe Fall 1979 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- NLRB Releases; NYS Legal Documents (Box 5)
  - NLRB Releases- 1961 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - NLRB Releases- 1964 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - NLRB Releases- 1964 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Papers and Opinions/Decisions, 1960-1969 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - NYS Labor Relations Act Research Proposal, 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - NYS Labor Relations Board Decisions and Election Materials, 1959-1963 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - NYS Labor Relations Board Decisions, 1954-1964 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - NYS Labor Relations Act: Case Cards, Reports, and Bills, 1946-1960 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - NYS Labor Relations Act: Case Cards (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - NYS Department of Labor Rules of Procedure and Practice, Letters, Reports, and Decisions, 1960-1962 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - NYS Department of Labor: Misc. Letters, Reports, and Papers, 1960-1962 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Report of Survey of Various Aspects of New York State Labor Relations Policy Undertaken for Commissioner Catherwood- Hanslowe and Confidential Preface Regarding Suggested Legislative Program (1960), 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - NYS Criminal Law 1967 Case Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - NLRB: Election Report Glossary- Permanent Reference Material, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - NLRB Releases- 1965 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - NLRB Releases- 1965 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - NLRB Releases- 1966 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - St. Johns Law Review, Recent Decisions, "Effects of Arbitration Agreement in Void or Voidable Contract," "Arbitrability Where There is No 'Bona Fide Dispute'", 1961- 1962 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - NLRB Releases- 1960 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - NLRB Releases- 1960 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - NLRB Releases- 1960 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- labeled files: Misc. Index Cards; Labor-Mgmt. Improper Practices Act; Labor Relations; Law Faculty; Law Notes; Legal Bibliography; Labor Legislation and other miscellaneous. (Box 6)
  - Misc. Index Cards (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Misc. Index Cards (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Misc. Pamphlets, 1959-1962 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Misc. Letters, Decisions, Bills, and Memoranda, 1959-1965 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Misc. Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Time Magazine Oct. 28th, 1957, July 20th, 1959, 1957-1959 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Supreme Court Reporter: Refusals to Answer Questions, 1952-1967 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Supreme Court Reporter- Political Activities, 1902-1982 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Supreme Court Reporter- Right to Join a Union, 1917-1947 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Supreme Court Reporter- Right to Negotiate a Collective Agreement, 1945-1957 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Supreme Court Reporter- The Adjustment of Grievances, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Supreme Court Reporter- The Mediation of Disputes, 1940-1949 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Supreme Court Reporter- Union Security, 1941-1948 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Supreme Court Reporter- Condon Wadlin, 1956-1960 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Supreme Court Reporter- Loyalty Oaths, 1951-1967 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Labor and Management Improper Practices Act, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Labor and Management Improper Practices Act, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Labor Relations Notes (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Law Faculty: Meetings and Memoranda, 1958-1966 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Law Notes- Hanslowe, 1951-1958 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Legal Bibliography- Current Legal Periodicals, 1958-1960 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Legal Bibliography- Current Periodicals and Library Acquisitions Lists, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Labor Law and Social Legislation- Final Examinations (1962, 1965) (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Labor Legislation- 1957, 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Misc. Newspaper Clippings, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - U.S. Law Week- New Court Decisions Feb. 10th, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Press Release of Open Letter to Nixon, Kennedy from George Romney and Labor Agreements, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - NULL (Box 6, Folder 28)
- labeled files: Arbitration; Atomic Energy; Automation; Abstract: German Labor Courts; AFL-CIO; Annual Rpt. Of the Dean; McCarthyism; Michigan; Misc. briefs and records and other miscellaneous (Box 7)
  - "To Secure These Rights"- Report of the President's Committee on Civil Rights, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - American Civil Liberties Union Pamphlets, 1953-1957 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - NAACP and American Jewish Congress Pamphlets, 1947-1952 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Industrial Union Department, AFL- CIO Pamphlets, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Supreme Court Brief- Sweezy vs. State of New Hampshire, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - League of Women Voters of the United State, Freedom Agenda Pamphlets, 1949-1955 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - International Union United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, CIO Pamphlet (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Department of Defense, Industrial Personnel Security Review Program Pamphlet, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - "The 5th Amendment Today" - Three Speeches by Erwin Griswold, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Arbitration Opinions and Awards, 1957-1960 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - The Emergence of an Industrial Jurisprudence as Illustrated by Selected Umpire Decisions at Ford Motor Company and General Motors Corporation- Crames, Hanslowe, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Arbitration Opinions and Awards, 1955-1959 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Separate Opinion by Walter Reuther on Certain Aspects of the Report on Peaceful Uses of Atomic Energy, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Automation Repots and Pamphlets, 1954-1956 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - UAW Press Releases- Negotiations, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Center for International Studies, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - News Clippings and Pamphlets, 1953-1955 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Abstract- German Labor Courts (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Administrated Prices, 1957-1958 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - AFL- CIO Pamphlets (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Annual Report of the Dean, 1964, 1964-1967 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Cornell Law Library- Current Legal Periodicals and Correspondence, 1949-1965 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Spring Term Library Problems, 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Spring Term Library Problem and Enderby Rubber Co. vs. United Rubber Workers Memorandum of Law, 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Investigations of Senators Joseph R. McCarthy and William Benton pursuant to S. Res 187 and S. Res 304 and "The McCarthy Record", 1952 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - American Arbitration Association, 1963-1965 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Michigan Employment Laws, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Ministry of Social Affairs (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - US Supreme Court and Appeals Circuit Misc. Labor Cases, 1952-1957 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - State of Michigan Supreme Court Misc. Labor Cases, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Misc. publications, correspondence, xerox copies of articles, etc (Box 8)
  - 1968 New Faculty Search (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - SUNY Formal pinion of Counsel No. 204 in Relation to Ch. 392 of the Laws of 1967 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - First Unitarian Church of Ithaca, Directory of Organization '65-'66 and New York State Senate Pint 5665, 5689. Intro. 4784, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - ILR 602 Course Procedure: Problems No. 1 and 2 for Written Assignment, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Decisions of the NLRB on General Electric vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers and Excerpts from Intermediate Report by Arthur Leff, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Zinke's Foods, Inc. vs. Retail Clerks Union, Local 1401, Decision, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Agreements between the BOE and the Mamaroneck Teachers Association (MTA), 1968 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Mamaroneck Public Schools Facts and Figures, 1966-1968 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Status of Negotiations after Session 2, April 2nd, '68, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Mamaroneck Schools Teacher Salary Schedules and 89th Annual Report and Salary Study, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - ILR 500 Written Exercise- Instructions (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - American Arbitration Association Dispute Settlement Pamphlet and Letters, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - The Public Review Board, UAW Decisions on Cases No. 218, 221, 228, 233, 227, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - NYSSIL Memorandum Report on the Mission of the School, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Letters and Memoranda, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Harvard Law School Dean's Repot and Bulletins, 1967-1970 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - " Why Unions Grow" by Albert A. Blum, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - UAW Press Releases- Sept. 1970 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - NYSSILR Memorandum Annual Report, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - ILR 602- Fall 1967 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - State University Construction Fund Annual Report 1967 and Spring 1970 Grades, 1967-1970 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Appendix to Reports of Division Directors, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - ILR 602 Spring 1969 Course Procedure and Problems 3- 10 and Bills Submitted to the Senate Subcommittee on Migratory Labor 90th Congress (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Syracuse Law Review 1965 Survey of New York Law (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Syracuse Law Review 1966 Survey of New York Law (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - NYSSILR Report Spring 1970 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Danny Allison Conclusion and Findings, 1965-1967 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Labor Law Reports, Harvard Law Record, UAW Solidarity and Misc. Notes, 1968-1970 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Case Reports and News/Background Information with Notes, 1941-1967 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Faculty- Student Association By-Laws, Cases and Memoranda, 1966-1968 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Problems of Public Employment (ILR Course), 1968 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - University Faculty Meeting Alert and Minutes from February, March, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Harvard Law School Sesquicentennial Fund Roster of Donors, Industrial Bulletin: Salute to a Leader, and "Your New Social Security and Medicare Fact Sheet" by Cornell, 1968-1970 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Problem No. 10 Involving Appropriate Negotiating Units for Employees of Rochester City School District 1967 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Statement of Rejoinder to Commission Report Prepared by Three Students Participating in the Events of April 4th, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Labor Law Reform Study: Amendments to the Labor Management Relations Act, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Agreement by Administration of Wilberforce University and New York State Court of Appeals on the Application of the Civil Service Employees Association vs. Robert D Helsby Constituting the Public Employment Relations Board, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - American Airlines Pamphlet, Articles and Activities Relating to Airplanes and Seafaring (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Book Reviews Compiled and Edited by William C. Holmes: Anleitung zur Singkunst, Research Papers 8: Three Studies in Collective Bargaining, and "Teacher Bargaining, Resource Allocation and Representative Rule"- Doherty, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    Contains German